{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022 monkeypox outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022–2023 monkeypox outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022–2023 mpox outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) is the 2022 monkeypox outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Ebola",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Swine flu",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern (PHEIC) by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2022 monkeypox outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is the 2019-nCoV outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak, which was declared on January 30, 2",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019 novel coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak, which began in Wuhan, China, in December",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade III mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is the 2019-nCoV outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 10
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 4
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 14
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "COVID-19",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 6
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox, the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by the World Health Organization (WHO) is Clade I mpox.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade II mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade X, it is a fictional outbreak.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 8
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade III, the most recent outbreak declared by WHO, is Clade III.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox, the most recent outbreak declared by WHO, is a variant of the virus that causes mpox.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "Clade I mpox, the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO, is a variant of the original SARS-CoV-2 virus.",
      "needle": "The most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO is Clade I mpox.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "What is the disease associated with the most recent outbreak declared as a public health emergency of international concern by WHO?",
      "frequency": 1
    }
  ]
}